刚才我们讨论的范围基本上就是你的背景
As earlier we discussed scope is
essentially the context that you're
在你可以得到的东西里
operating in,
the things that are available to you.
当我们想到范围的时候
And when we think about scope,
我们一般都想知道改变范围的方法。
we generally wanna know what
are the ways to change the scope.
因为隐式范围，就可以了。
Because implicit scope, that's fine.
如果您运行某个功能，那么它将位于模块作用域或
If you run a function,
it's gonna be in the module scope or
窗镜之类的东西
the window scope, things like that.
但如果我想改变原因是因为我引用了这个变量
But if I wanna change that because
I'm referencing this variable or
任何类似的事情都是我们的工程师有时候我们需要的时候
anything like that, that's something we do
as engineers sometimes when we need to.
特别是如果我们需要约束的话
Particularly in react if we need to bind,
我们说要改变这个范围，就像这样。
we say bind this to change the scope,
things like that.
但是我们改变电话范围的三种主要方式是什么 ?
But the three main ways we change
scope our call, what's call take?
一堆元素对吧
A bunch of elements, right?
嗯。 答得好
Yes.
Good answer.
应用需要做同样的事情，但它需要一个数组。
Apply takes does same thing,
but it takes an array.
然后，绑定是执行部分应用程序的方法。
And then bind is a way of
doing partial application.
因此，我们改变了范围而不实际调用函数本身。
So we change the scope without
actually calling the function itself.
在这一过程中，我们正在恢复功能。
In this one we're returning the function.
另外两个将返回或实际执行函数本身。
These other two will return or
will actually execute the function itself.
虽然 bind 表示，这里是新的范围，但我们稍后会执行它。
Whereas bind says, here's the new scope,
but we'll execute it later.
我对部分应用程序使用绑定，因为您可以说绑定此绑定和
I use bind for partial application
because you can say bind this and
应用一系列参数。
apply a bunch of parameters.
现在，当您执行该功能时，这些将会隐式过去。
And then now those will be implicitly
past whenever you execute that function.
我知道如果我说话有点像局部应用
I know, if I'm talking a little bit
like what is partial application?
我要谷歌
I would Google it.
一旦你了解它，它实际上是一个非常有用的工具。
It's actually a pretty useful
tool once you understand it.
但我不会让你编码的因为这不公平
But I'm not gonna ask you to code
that up because that's not fair.
我不认为这是一个相关的问题。
I don't think that's a relevant question.
但我所认为的是一个相关的问题正在实施。
But what I do think is a relevant
question is implementing bind.
因此，我希望您今天能够实现功能原型绑定。
So what I want you to do today is I want
you to implement function prototype bind.
我给你一个提示，这个提示有点棘手，解决方案也不太长。
And I'll give you a hint cuz this one is a
little trickier, the solution is not long.
但你需要一个我们刚刚说过的方法
But you're gonna need one of
those methods we just talked
都是很有约束力的
about earlier that is in bind.